[{"answer": " Is that for me", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Madam my friend's car is to be brought", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " For me", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Madam my friend's car is not to be brought", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Good evening", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You're tired. I can see that", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You are ill", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It is not stage fright", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Last night?... There was no applause", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " There was", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, don't go", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, can anyone engage you for the evening", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " General Director Preysing!  my friend, when I was sixteen years old, I started as an office boy in that man's factory", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Do I know him", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No news from that place yet", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You're a very unusual stenographer", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Moreover...", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What brown hands you have", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Skiing?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You're a little too fast", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I understand you perfectly", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Cotton Company", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " ...weight into the balance..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Now listen to me. The others are getting suspicious of you. I was on the telephone to that place today, they think you're scared", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You've been waiting your chance. You're too much of a gentleman", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Get out and leave it to me... be ready to leave on the night train for that place..", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "With the pearls", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I suppose I can cancel the that place engagement", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You'll be very much alone, my dear madame. This is the end.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Why do you hide in my room", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Because you love me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " And", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Go away. Who are you", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You could love me. It is so long since I have heard that word. Nobody has loved me for a long time. It is so ic", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm not going", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That is not so", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I want to be alone", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I want to be alone", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Why do you smile", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What can you see", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " that place", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " We have a good many connections in that place, naturally", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Tentative my foot", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Of course you took the initiative", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Good morning, gentlemen", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "But the situation is perfectly clear, If you will allow me", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " We did not approach you", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "And I said we didn't", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Can't", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Why later", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "I've told you three times", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "No, he did not", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I'm going to change and we'll meet for a drink in the Yellow Room", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " Where the music's playing and the ladies are..", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Oh no", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Gentlemen, I am now free to announce...  ...that the deal between my firm and the that place has been successfully negotiated", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " What's the matter with you", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "What's bluff", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "No one would have thought it of me. I've been getting rusty in that place. Well, if bluff is what the world wants I guess I can put up as big a bluff as anyone. From now on...", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Say it", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I want to see her, I want to do some dictating", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "For me?", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "A that place flip, that sounds very nice", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "You like music", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": " A man might what", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "What have you been doing all day", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Chasing what", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You must learn as quickly as your time allows", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": " I'm always alone", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "That was lovely", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I'll do anything for you", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Perhaps this evening, my friend, we could go to the Casino", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Broke", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "How", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You might find a bullet through that head..", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Don't", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": " No", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "All right then", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "For tonight.", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Aha!", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Made a mistake", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "It seems that he was a thief and an imposter", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "Perhaps he really was a burglar", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "So did I. He was friendly to me as no man ever was", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "He was in desperate straits. He'd been trying to raise money all day. He laughed", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": " And now we travel, Flaemmchen... Glad", "docId": "Grand-Hotel.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": " Is the bill ready", "qsentId": 98}]